<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Picasso Live Movies Tv Tips</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">HomeActivity</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>

    <string name="subscriptionText">
        Viewing Pikashow is pretty simple, all you need is an internet connection. The Pikashow content is available on the website and app. Although some content is free. Some might require a login, which is free. However, the free content is very limited and contain ads. The persistent interruptions will make you reconsider the free subscription. In case the Pikashow app is not available in a certain area. Using a VPN to ping the location to a country where the Pikashow app is available might help.


    </string>
    <string name="wohApna">
        Although the content can be accessed from the website as well(which runs as smoothly as the application). The Pikashow app comes with its own benefits. Easily available on all app stores(play store, apple store), it unlocks many features which are not available on the website. For instance, certain content is not available for free on the website but is on the application. Such as, the English premier league(soccer) live matches can be viewed for free on the mobile app but need premium access on the website.

    </string>
    <string name="manmohiniText">
         One of the largest entertainment networks in the world, the star network targets a very large audience. As it covers content relevant to almost all parts of the globe. From sporting events, to internationally released movies and TV shows. Earlier the Pikashow App was available and accessible to all parts of the world ( despite being exclusively launched in India). However, recently the app is only available in three countries. India America Canada

  </string>
   <string name="ishqSubhanAllah">
       With more producers focusing to put their work on exclusive display, new weekly episodes and much-anticipated content might be lost to the user. Do not worry, Pikashow app got you covered. The application provides an option to add the content to a wish list. This will allow the Pikashow app to notify you whenever the new content is available or to buy a subscription on time. (if you are out of one). The feature also acts as a bookmark for shows that you might be interested in for later viewing.
   </string>

    <string name="tujhseHai">
       The most recent update of the Pikashow App came with a new feature. With cricket events such as IPL and ICC cricket world cup approaches, the app offered a unique experience to the user. The viewers, if not on full-screen mode, could see certain options on the bottom of their screens. These options are the likely occurrences on the next ball, 1/2/3 or 4/6 or wicket or no/wide ball. Correctly predicting the outcome grants the user points. The more unlikely the outcome the higher the points. Each over serves as a round and at the end of each round, the scores are compiled. Multipliers are also added on consecutive correct guesses.
    </string>

    <string name="piyaAlbela">
       Here is the tricky part. The points collected are only valid if you complete the rounds or you stick around till the end of the match. The tie-ups with other apps allow Hostar app to give away many prizes. The points earned during the match work as an app currency and can be used for micro transactions to buy cash backs and discounts. Needless to say, there is a 1st, 2nd, 3rd prize but the Pikashow app ensures that each participant gets something and comes back to try their luck again. The prizes are only available for live events
    </string>

    <string name="appbar_scrolling_view_behavior">com.google.android.material.appbar.AppBarLayout$ScrollingViewBehavior</string>
    <string name="bottom_sheet_behavior">com.google.android.material.bottomsheet.BottomSheetBehavior</string>
    <string name="bottomsheet_action_expand_halfway">Expand halfway</string>
    <string name="character_counter_content_description">Characters entered %1$d of %2$d</string>
    <string name="character_counter_overflowed_content_description">Character limit exceeded %1$d of %2$d</string>
    <string name="character_counter_pattern">%1$d/%2$d</string>
    <string name="chip_text">Chip text</string>
    <string name="clear_text_end_icon_content_description">Clear text</string>
    <string name="com_mopub_nativeads_sponsored_by">Sponsored by %s</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_unknown_issue">%1$s is having trouble with Google Play services. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="ddsonysports">Star has rights to cover almost all major sporting events occurring around the world. Some are covered live simultaneously, such as in the case of soccer; when multiple teams play at the same time. Pikashow app has a sports option for you, to skip all the content and jump right into your favorite sport. The live and most popular events are listed on the top. The sports tab also provides the option of viewing the highlights of any match or event you might have missed. Multiple events of the same sports may occur at the same time. So the tab has sub-categories in the form of the name of the sport, like cricket, football, etc.</string>
    <string name="default_notification_channel_name">Now playing</string>
    <string name="discrip1">Here is the tricky part. The points collected are only valid if you complete the rounds or you stick around till the end of the match. The tie-ups with other apps allow Hostar app to give away many prizes. The points earned during the match work as an app currency and can be used for micro transactions to buy cash backs and discounts. Needless to say, there is a 1st, 2nd, 3rd prize but the Pikashow app ensures that each participant gets something and comes back to try their luck again. The prizes are only available for live events</string>
    <string name="discrip2">Star has rights to cover almost all major sporting events occurring around the world. Some are covered live simultaneously, such as in the case of soccer; when multiple teams play at the same time. Pikashow app has a sports option for you, to skip all the content and jump right into your favorite sport. The live and most popular events are listed on the top. The sports tab also provides the option of viewing the highlights of any match or event you might have missed. Multiple events of the same sports may occur at the same time. So the tab has sub-categories in the form of the name of the sport, like cricket, football, etc.</string>
    <string name="discrip3">Pikashow app has a huge library of movies. From latest releases to the old classics. From international blockbusters such as the Avengers to lesser-known domestic films. However, the movies may not be available in all regions, due to copyright infringement. The movies tab is systematically subdivided into categories such as Action, comedy, for kids, popular, new on Pikashow, Biopic and so on. Interestingly; based on your previous choices, the app also provides a subcategory called top picks for you.</string>
    <string name="discrip4">The news tab in the app is very interesting. It provides the option of viewing the news channels live, mostly the channels which are already free to air. It also plays the top headlines on queue as soon as you land on the news tab home. Although, various news outlets are available in multiple languages. The top suggested are the ones from your own country and in the native language by default. But differs if the settings have been customized. The network also has an in house news outlet. It is interesting because there is no prominent news channel in the star network, only entertainment, and sports.</string>
    <string name="discrip5">Viewing Pikashow is pretty simple, all you need is an internet connection. The Pikashow content is available on the website and app. Although some content is free. Some might require a login, which is free. However, the free content is very limited and contain ads. The persistent interruptions will make you reconsider the free subscription. In case the Pikashow app is not available in a certain area. Using a VPN to ping the location to a country where the Pikashow app is available might help.</string>
    <string name="discrip6">With more producers focusing to put their work on exclusive display, new weekly episodes and much-anticipated content might be lost to the user. Do not worry, Pikashow app got you covered. The application provides an option to add the content to a wish list. This will allow the Pikashow app to notify you whenever the new content is available or to buy a subscription on time. (if you are out of one). The feature also acts as a bookmark for shows that you might be interested in for later viewing.</string>
    <string name="discrip7">The membership let users access all Pikashow originals and exclusive shows or videos. The plan also includes movies, ALT Balaji Shows, Zindagi TV Shows, Kids, Live TV, and TV shows before they are telecasted on TV. Pikashow Premium members also get to watch videos on five different devices at a time.</string>
    <string name="discrip8">The most recent update of the Pikashow App came with a new feature. With cricket events such as IPL and ICC cricket world cup approaches, the app offered a unique experience to the user. The viewers, if not on full-screen mode, could see certain options on the bottom of their screens. These options are the likely occurrences on the next ball, 1/2/3 or 4/6 or wicket or no/wide ball. Correctly predicting the outcome grants the user points. The more unlikely the outcome the higher the points. Each over serves as a round and at the end of each round, the scores are compiled. Multipliers are also added on consecutive correct guesses.</string>
    <string name="discrip9">Here is the tricky part. The points collected are only valid if you complete the rounds or you stick around till the end of the match. The tie-ups with other apps allow Hostar app to give away many prizes. The points earned during the match work as an app currency and can be used for micro transactions to buy cash backs and discounts. Needless to say, there is a 1st, 2nd, 3rd prize but the Pikashow app ensures that each participant gets something and comes back to try their luck again. The prizes are only available for live events</string>
    <string name="error_icon_content_description">Error</string>
    <string name="exposed_dropdown_menu_content_description">Show dropdown menu</string>
    <string name="fab_transformation_scrim_behavior">com.google.android.material.transformation.FabTransformationScrimBehavior</string>
    <string name="fab_transformation_sheet_behavior">com.google.android.material.transformation.FabTransformationSheetBehavior</string>
    <string name="guide1">How To Watch Pikashow</string>
    <string name="guide2">Movies Pikashow</string>
    <string name="guide3">News Pikashow</string>
    <string name="guide4">Sport Pikashow?</string>
    <string name="guide5">Point Pikashow?</string>
    <string name="guide6">Play Pikashow?</string>
    <string name="guide7">Wishlist Pikashow?</string>
    <string name="guide8">Availability Pikashow</string>
    <string name="guj_news">News is information about current events. This may be provided through many different media: word of mouth, printing, postal systems, broadcasting, electronic communication, or through the testimony of observers and witnesses to events. Common topics for news reports include war, government, politics, education, health, the environment, economy, business, fashion, and entertainment, as well as athletic events, quirky or unusual events. Government proclamations, concerning royal ceremonies, laws, taxes, public health, and criminals, have been dubbed news since ancient times.</string>
    <string name="hide_bottom_view_on_scroll_behavior">com.google.android.material.behavior.HideBottomViewOnScrollBehavior</string>
    <string name="icon_content_description">Dialog Icon</string>
    <string name="indiatv">Here is the tricky part. The points collected are only valid if you complete the rounds or you stick around till the end of the match. The tie-ups with other apps allow Hostar app to give away many prizes. The points earned during the match work as an app currency and can be used for micro transactions to buy cash backs and discounts. Needless to say, there is a 1st, 2nd, 3rd prize but the Pikashow app ensures that each participant gets something and comes back to try their luck again. The prizes are only available for live events</string>
    <string name="item_view_role_description">Tab</string>



</resources>