<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Thop TV-Live Cricket</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">HomeActivity</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>

    <string name="subscriptionText">
         ThopTV alternative, RedBox TV is a free live streaming program that allows users to watch shows and sports games in a variety of quality options based on their preferences.


    </string>
    <string name="wohApna">
         a dime to watch free live Indian channels and it offers live streaming of TV shows, sports, movies, and other content for free. Redbox includes over 1000 TV channels, all of which offer free SD and HD programming. One of the nicest features is that Redbox TV is a brilliant ThopTV alternative for iOS and Android alike.

    </string>
    <string name="manmohiniText">
         performs great as a ThopTV alternative that allows you to enjoy the convenience of streaming any film or TV show for free, especially regional Indian content.

  </string>
   <string name="ishqSubhanAllah">
       With more producers focusing to put their work on exclusive display, new weekly episodes and much-anticipated content might be lost to the user. Do not worry, Pikashow app got you covered. The application provides an option to add the content to a wish list. This will allow the Pikashow app to notify you whenever the new content is available or to buy a subscription on time. (if you are out of one). The feature also acts as a bookmark for shows that you might be interested in for later viewing.
   </string>

    <string name="tujhseHai">
       Nonetheless, it is the unreliability of such apps that make their futures bleak; a TV show you were watching yesterday may not be accessible today if the app is taken down, similar to ThopTV. Moreover, OTT platforms, like Netflix, are applying new means to gain and retain their subscribers by alterations to their subscription models by lowering costs in a bid to be more accessible. Also in terms of privacy and security, paid subscriptions for OTT platforms ensure that your device is not vulnerable to malware and hackers, which is likely to occur by downloading APK files from untrustworthy sources. The future of thop tv alternative streaming sources like Hunk TV, Oreo TV, and others can be deemed volatile, albeit inexpensive.
    </string>

    <string name="piyaAlbela">
       A Thop TV like app, LiveNet TV is your solution to selecting and watching from a wide assortment of TV shows across hundreds of channels. Entertainment, sports, news, kids, action, movies, and other genres are all available on Live NetTV and you can choose the channels supported in your country. It provides you with over 800 live channels in a variety of categories such as news, movies, sports, entertainment, cooking, children’s programming, and religious programs, which makes it an app like Thop TV with content suited to your likes.
    </string>

    <string name="appbar_scrolling_view_behavior">com.google.android.material.appbar.AppBarLayout$ScrollingViewBehavior</string>
    <string name="bottom_sheet_behavior">com.google.android.material.bottomsheet.BottomSheetBehavior</string>
    <string name="bottomsheet_action_expand_halfway">Expand halfway</string>
    <string name="character_counter_content_description">Characters entered %1$d of %2$d</string>
    <string name="character_counter_overflowed_content_description">Character limit exceeded %1$d of %2$d</string>
    <string name="character_counter_pattern">%1$d/%2$d</string>
    <string name="chip_text">Chip text</string>
    <string name="clear_text_end_icon_content_description">Clear text</string>
    <string name="com_mopub_nativeads_sponsored_by">Sponsored by %s</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_unknown_issue">%1$s is having trouble with Google Play services. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="ddsonysports">the top Thoptv alternatives to watch live sports, TV shows, and trending movies from across the world. Users are enthusiastic about the excellent streaming options available on the ThopTV live cricket TV App. Other than apps like ThopTV, a live streaming option like ThopTV live cricket APK comes first because of its incredible capabilities that no other software in this category has, such as the ability to download live TV shows, the ability to watch movies online, and more.</string>
    <string name="default_notification_channel_name">Now playing</string>
    <string name="discrip1">We provide match odds and session based on analysis and knowledge that we have collected from our various sources. We do not support/encourage any type of betting either legal or illegal.we are not responsible if betting is not legal in the country of our respective users and/or the respective user do any kind of illegal betting thereof.This app is not for betting or supporting betting,this app is meant only for fun and entertainment purpose.</string>
    <string name="discrip2">A free Android TV software that lets you watch free episodes, movies, and live TV without having to sign up for anything. In real-time, you’ll be able to watch your favorite TV or movie. Alternatively, you can download it to your phone and watch it at a later time. You may also create a favorites list to organize and view your favorite shows at any time. It also has a feature that allows you to stream content in whichever quality you desire, including Full HD 1080p, 2K, and even 4K.</string>
    <string name="discrip3">is a one-of-a-kind ThopTV alternative app that includes categories for Hotstar, Jio, and Zee5, as well as Zee5 Original Shows. It is a ThopTV like app that allows users to access free live TV on Android devices, and it is immensely popular among those who wish to watch live TV for free, as it provides high-quality content.</string>
    <string name="discrip4">One of the apps like ThopTV is ThopTV live cricket, which has access to the most recent movies and television episodes. It provides you with the best filters, such as IMDB score, Metacritic ratings, and so on. It updates its database with new shows automatically, and you can watch trailers, movies, and TV shows on ThopTV live cricket without having to go elsewhere. One of the best features of this software is the ability to automatically update your dashboard with new movies and episodes and display any show’s ratings in real-time.</string>
    <string name="discrip5">ThopTV alternative and an Android OTT software that features content from over five different paid OTT platforms. To replace all other streaming platforms, one can simply make use of the free thop tv like apps </string>
    <string name="discrip6">This app contains almost all TV and movie features, making it a wonderful and inexpensive thop tv alternative to costly subscriptions available on Android, Windows, Mac, and Linux devices. However, </string>
    <string name="discrip7">This app contains almost all TV and movie features, making it a wonderful and inexpensive thop tv alternative to costly subscriptions available on Android, Windows, Mac, and Linux devices. However, after its discontinuation in July 2021 post, a 2 year run for a monthly fee of Rs. 35, content consumers have been on the lookout for Thop TV like apps that provides access to live cricket, new movies, TV shows, and live channels</string>
    <string name="discrip8">ThopTV live cricket is undoubtedly a great option for a ThopTV similar app. The ThopTV live cricket  app allows you to watch high-definition movies and TV episodes on your Android phone. This program offers over 1000+ free TV channels, providing you with a vast amount of enjoyment. ThopTV live cricket  offers no-cost services and there is no need to register to watch live streaming channels. You need to simply download ThopTV live cricket  and start watching your favorite TV shows, movies, and web series.</string>
    <string name="discrip9">They’ve also divided the channels into categories like Kids, Music, Movies, News, Sports, and so on. This thop tv like apps will provide you with different streaming options for Live TV Channels and as feasible, new channels and links are added and updated. From a country-by-country channel list, you can select from a wide number of channels.</string>
    <string name="error_icon_content_description">Error</string>
    <string name="exposed_dropdown_menu_content_description">Show dropdown menu</string>
    <string name="fab_transformation_scrim_behavior">com.google.android.material.transformation.FabTransformationScrimBehavior</string>
    <string name="fab_transformation_sheet_behavior">com.google.android.material.transformation.FabTransformationSheetBehavior</string>
    <string name="guide1">ThopTv Live Score</string>
    <string name="guide2">Live Line</string>
    <string name="guide3">Live Matches</string>
    <string name="guide4">Match Odds</string>
    <string name="guide5">Stats</string>
    <string name="guide6">Score Card?</string>
    <string name="guide7">UpComing Matches</string>
    <string name="guide8">Upcoming</string>
    <string name="guj_news">News is information about current events. This may be provided through many different media: word of mouth, printing, postal systems, broadcasting, electronic communication, or through the testimony of observers and witnesses to events. Common topics for news reports include war, government, politics, education, health, the environment, economy, business, fashion, and entertainment, as well as athletic events, quirky or unusual events. Government proclamations, concerning royal ceremonies, laws, taxes, public health, and criminals, have been dubbed news since ancient times.</string>
    <string name="hide_bottom_view_on_scroll_behavior">com.google.android.material.behavior.HideBottomViewOnScrollBehavior</string>
    <string name="icon_content_description">Dialog Icon</string>
    <string name="indiatv">Here is the tricky part. The points collected are only valid if you complete the rounds or you stick around till the end of the match. The tie-ups with other apps allow Hostar app to give away many prizes. The points earned during the match work as an app currency and can be used for micro transactions to buy cash backs and discounts. Needless to say, there is a 1st, 2nd, 3rd prize but the Pikashow app ensures that each participant gets something and comes back to try their luck again. The prizes are only available for live events</string>
    <string name="item_view_role_description">Tab</string>



</resources>