<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Zee Anmol Tv Serials Guide</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">HomeActivity</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>

    <string name="subscriptionText">
        Latest Original Shows  Movies Only On ZEEAnmol. Select From Multiple Genres @ ₹1/3 months. Enjoy Exclusive Originals as well as Popular Movies and TV shows on ZEEAnmol. Subscribe Now. Easy Streaming. 4500+ Blockbuster Movies. ₹100 Cashback with Paytm.


    </string>
    <string name="wohApna">
        1) What is the story of woh Apna Sa? Plot. Aditya Jindal has a troubled marriage with the selfish Nisha Verma but remains with her for their daughters Chinni and Binni as well as his family who think highly of Nisha. Later, Jhanvi Agarwal enters Adityas life.

2) Who is Jia in kindred hearts? KINDRED HEARTS FULL STORY- 20 Years After Aditya and Jhanvi are reborn as Arjun Sinh and Jia Mehra respectively. Jia is a model in London and Arjun is a pretty cheat. Aditya and nishas elder daughter Chinni Jindal has grown up hating Nisha and misses Jhanvi and Aditya.

3) What happen in kindred heart? After a long investigation, Jia finally gets justice for Arjuns death when Nisha finally reveals that she had killed him. As she is about to be arrested, she slips and falls to her death. The show ends with Jia (who is now Arjuns widow) starting a new life with Inspector Krishna Shekhawat (Kunal Karan Kapoor).

4) How Rahul Vaidya and Disha Parmar met? While some media reports suggest that Rahul and Disha first met each other via a common friend. In another media interview with Disha, the actress revealed that "I liked a song by him and commented Loved it on the post."The sweet little internet talk became the start of their Love Life.

5) Is Sudeep Sahir Punjabi?

Well, in conversation with her, Sayantani also mentioned how she has not played a Punjabi character and since Sudeep (Sahir) and the director of the show is a Punjabi, they help her in getting the accent right.
    </string>
    <string name="manmohiniText">
        1) Has Manmohini ended?

The series was last broadcast on 24 March 2020 when the remaining episodes were aired. It was intended to end in April 2020 but had to be postponed due to the pandemic. The show resumed on 14 July 2020 with brand new episodes, ending on 22 July 2020.

2) Who is Amar in Manmohini?

Amar is Ram and Siya is son. Shiv and Amar have emotional moment. Shiv tells Amar that Ananya is not married to him. He asks Amar to keep his secret.

3) What is the story of serial Manmohini? Manmohini is a supernatural romantic thriller starring Reyhna Pandit as a 500-year-old witch. The witch, named Mohini, is waiting to reunite with her lover who is reborn as Ram. Mohini leaves no stone unturned to get Ram to love her while Siya too puts up a good fight to save her husband and their marriage.

4) What is Mohini in Curse of the sand real name? A magician named Mohini (Reyna Pandit) has been waiting for her unrequited love for 500 years, the Rana Saa, who was born again as RAM (Ankit Siwach).

5) Is Vaishali Takkar married? Actor Vaishali Takkar, who starred in popular TV shows such as Sasural Simar Ka and Yeh Rishta Kya Kehlata Hai, has got engaged to Dr Abhinandan Singh. The actor shared the news on Instagram. What\'s yours will Ultimately find you even from another end of the world Rokafied To this Wonderful Man Dr.

6) What happen Karam Rajpal and Shivaleeka? Shivaleeka had announced roka engagement with Naamkarann actor Karam Rajpal in 2018. But soon before Shivaleeka was about to make her Bollywood debut, she claimed to be single. The couple refuted all roka engagement reports calling it a hoax and said they are just friends.
  </string>
   <string name="ishqSubhanAllah">
        1) Why did Zara leave Ishq Subhan Allah? The young actress recently shared her happiness of being back on Ishq Subhan Allah sets and team. She said, Though I bid goodbye to the show for some personal commitments, somewhere at the bottom of my heart, this show was always my baby. It is an absolute delight to return as Zara.

2) Is Eisha Singh coming back to Zaras nikah? Eisha Singh has returned to Ishq Subhan Allah as Zara. The actress recently started shooting for the show. Her co-star Adnan Khan is one of the happiest with her comeback. In an exclusive chat with India Today Television, Adnan Khan shared how he welcomed Eisha on the sets.

3) Is Eisha Singh coming back to Ishq Subhan Allah? After the TV show went on hiatus during the lockdown in March, Eisha Singh is back once again on the show and stars alongside Adnan Khan to give the fans their old Kabir and Zara! Watch a recap of Zara and Kabirs love story in Ishq Subhan Allah here.

4) How Zaras nikah will end? While worsening her condition under the pretense of taking care of her, Rukhsaars evil plans are discovered by Ayesha on Zaras wedding day, but before exposing her, Rukhsaar smothers Ayesha with a pillow and kills her.

5) Is Zara dead in Zara nikah 2021? Salma found out her Zara is still alive. Kabir beg Zara and to meet her mom at least once but she refuse. Nargis agree to meet Salma but not as her daughter. Irfan sees Zara and gets emotional.

6) What is the story of Ishq Subhan Allah? Set against a Muslim backdrop, Ishq Subhan Allah addresses contemporary political, religious, and social issues such as triple talaq (divorce) and Sharia laws. Kabeer Ahmed and Zara Siddiqui (Eisha Singh) are both devout followers of Islam but interpret the
   </string>

    <string name="tujhseHai">
        1) When was Tujhse Hai Raabta started? It was premiered on 3 September 2018 and telecast on the time slot of 8:30 PM. Tujhse Hai Raabta 2nd September 2020 Written Episode, Written Update on TellyUpdates.com. The show will be a romantic tale and will be founded on an affection triangle.

2) Why did Malhar shoot Kalyani?

Tujhse Hai Raabta Malhar shoots Kalyani 12th August Malhar wants Kalyani to stop Trilok, who is the only person knowing about Moksh. They get hindered by the snakes.She thinks to save him from the snakes first. She gets the milk to attract the snakes and save Malhar.

3) Is Malhar alive in Tujhse Hai Raabta? Malhar is alive! With Shera, Kalyani reaches Goa in search of Malhar. Malhar works to nab a terrorist organisation. Now, viewers in India can watch Tujhse Hai Raabta episodes before their TV telecast on ZEE5!

4) Who killed Malhar?

During the war Khanderao Holkar, son of Malhar Rao Holkar, was one day inspecting his army in an open palanquin, when he was fired upon from the fort. The cannonball hit and killed him on 24 March 1754. Malhar Rao was infuriated by the death of his only son and wanted to take revenge.

5) Is Shera actually Malhar?

Kalyani comes to the PS and asks Pawar and tells him that the guy is not Malhar ji, but Shera. She met him somewhere and brought it as Malhar ji, so that she can get back her son and also she can find about Malhars real murderer. She says Shera is not a nice guy and eloped with the idol.

6) Why did Shagun leave Tujhse Hai Raabta? I want to do reality shows now. I really want to enter the Bigg Boss house. I am confident that if I become a part of the show, I will surely win the trophy, he added.
    </string>

    <string name="piyaAlbela">
        1) How does Piyaa Albela end? So how will Piyaa Albela bid adieu its viewers? According to our sources, the show will end on a happy note. Naren (Akshay) and Pooja (Sheen) remarry, while Supriya kills Angraj (Sahil Uppal). In addition, before the show ends, viewers will see Rachel-Arjun and Sanish-Kiran tying the knot.

2) What is the story of Piya Albela? Plot. The show revolves around Naren Vyas (Akshay Mhatre) and Pooja Goel (Sheen Dass). Naren is on the path of spirituality, living as a recluse and cut off from worldly activities. Naren and Pooja become best friends, and Pooja falls in love with him after he saves her from being raped by his cousin Rahul.

3) Who is Bandhu in Piya Albela? Moving ahead, it is revealed that Bandhu is none other than Mayans father and is teamed up with Guruji to do something big amid Pooja and Narens wedlock.

4) Is Naren dead in Piya Albela? Pooja thus ends up killing Naren and Angraaj laughs out loud as it is his victory and now Pooja will be his. Pooja is all shattered that she killed her Naren with her ow hands and lashes at Rahul and Surbhi for supporting Angraaj.

5) Who killed Anuj in Piya Albela? Piya Albela 14th June 2018 Written Episode Update: Anuj dies and Angraj falls in the river. The Episode starts with Anuj shooting at Angraj although Naren and Pooja try to stop him, but in vain. He shoots at him again on his shoulder. Naren takes out his gun and shoots at Anuj thrice.

6) Is Sheen Dass Bengali?

Sheen Dass belongs to a Kashmiri Pandit Family. Sheen is the daughter of Bharat Dass and Savita Dass. Sheen has an elder sister, Swati Dass
    </string>

    <string name="appbar_scrolling_view_behavior">com.google.android.material.appbar.AppBarLayout$ScrollingViewBehavior</string>
    <string name="bottom_sheet_behavior">com.google.android.material.bottomsheet.BottomSheetBehavior</string>
    <string name="bottomsheet_action_expand_halfway">Expand halfway</string>
    <string name="character_counter_content_description">Characters entered %1$d of %2$d</string>
    <string name="character_counter_overflowed_content_description">Character limit exceeded %1$d of %2$d</string>
    <string name="character_counter_pattern">%1$d/%2$d</string>
    <string name="chip_text">Chip text</string>
    <string name="clear_text_end_icon_content_description">Clear text</string>
    <string name="com_mopub_nativeads_sponsored_by">Sponsored by %s</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_unknown_issue">%1$s is having trouble with Google Play services. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="ddsonysports">DD Sports is an Indian state-owned sports TV channel telecasting from Central Production Centre Delhi, India. DD Sports was launched on 18 March 1998. In the beginning, it broadcast sports programmes for six hours a day, which was increased to 12 hours in 1999. From 1 June 2000, DD Sports became a round-the-clock satellite channel. It was an encrypted pay channel between 2000 and 2003, and on 15 July 2003, it became the only free-to-air sports channel in the country.</string>
    <string name="default_notification_channel_name">Now playing</string>
    <string name="discrip1">To enjoy an ad-free experience and more, you will need to purchase a subscription. Click here to view our Premium Subscription Plans. Our Subscription offerings start as low as Rs. 1 a day!</string>
    <string name="discrip2">The ZEE5 Premium subscription is priced in India at Rs 999; however, with a limited period offer, it is currently available at Rs 499. The subscription will be valid for 12 months and supports three screens at a time.</string>
    <string name="discrip3">This issue typically points to a weak Internet connection. ... The video quality would adapt to the speed of your Internet connection to reduce buffering.</string>
    <string name="discrip4">Under (Language and) Settings, click / tap on Authenticate Device. Enter the code you see on your TV screen and click / tap on Authenticate. Click Continue on your TV screen to start enjoying ZEE5!</string>
    <string name="discrip5">ZEEPLEX is a premium movie-on-demand service where users can watch blockbuster movies by renting them. On the other hand, ZEE5 is a streaming platform where users will find movies, web series, TV shows across various languages. Yes! ZEEPLEX and ZEE5 premium are different from each other.</string>
    <string name="discrip6">Zee5 is worst in terms of performance, switching between movie, tv, news etc is really a difficult job. There is much put into this app that it seems not able to handle the load. Zee should make it lighter and faster by splitting the features into multiple apps.</string>
    <string name="discrip7">The membership let users access all Zee5 originals and exclusive shows or videos. The plan also includes movies, ALT Balaji Shows, Zindagi TV Shows, Kids, Live TV, and TV shows before they are telecasted on TV. Zee5 Premium members also get to watch videos on five different devices at a time.</string>
    <string name="discrip8">Both the apps have curated content but the Prime Video app gives you a richer experience with high-budget shows and movies, whereas Zee5 gives you access to some live channels and has more language options available.</string>
    <string name="discrip9">Zee5 offers both free and premium content streaming options. For free streaming, you can simply register yourself and start right away. However, for streaming premium content, you have to subscribe to its premium service first.</string>
    <string name="error_icon_content_description">Error</string>
    <string name="exposed_dropdown_menu_content_description">Show dropdown menu</string>
    <string name="fab_transformation_scrim_behavior">com.google.android.material.transformation.FabTransformationScrimBehavior</string>
    <string name="fab_transformation_sheet_behavior">com.google.android.material.transformation.FabTransformationSheetBehavior</string>
    <string name="guide1">How can I watch ZEE5 without ads?</string>
    <string name="guide2">How much does ZEE5 cost?</string>
    <string name="guide3">Why is ZEE5 buffering?</string>
    <string name="guide4">How do I get my ZEE5 TV code?</string>
    <string name="guide5">Is ZEE5 and Zeeplex same?</string>
    <string name="guide6">Is Zee5 any good?</string>
    <string name="guide7">What is Zee5 premium?</string>
    <string name="guide8">Which is better Zee5 or Amazon Prime?</string>
    <string name="guj_news">News is information about current events. This may be provided through many different media: word of mouth, printing, postal systems, broadcasting, electronic communication, or through the testimony of observers and witnesses to events. Common topics for news reports include war, government, politics, education, health, the environment, economy, business, fashion, and entertainment, as well as athletic events, quirky or unusual events. Government proclamations, concerning royal ceremonies, laws, taxes, public health, and criminals, have been dubbed news since ancient times.</string>
    <string name="hide_bottom_view_on_scroll_behavior">com.google.android.material.behavior.HideBottomViewOnScrollBehavior</string>
    <string name="icon_content_description">Dialog Icon</string>
    <string name="indiatv">India TV is a Hindi news channel based in Noida, Uttar Pradesh, India. The channel was launched on 20 May 2004 by Rajat Sharma and wife Ritu Dhawan. The channel is a subsidiary of Independent News Service, which was co-founded by Sharma and Dhawan in 1997. Prior to launching India TV, Rajat Sharma was a previously the anchor of Aap Ki Adalat on Zee News and Janata Ki Adalat on Star News.</string>
    <string name="item_view_role_description">Tab</string>



</resources>